For us and the kids and I will make it a
home together.
And Michael?
I would never cut Michael out of their
lives the way he did to me. He is their
father and the kids would miss him
terribly.
But he is only going to see them on my
terms.
>> Okay, sounds wonderful.
>> It does, doesn't it?
I have been on the defensive for so
long.
But soon my kids will be with me and I
will be the one making the decisions
from now on.
>> Moment.
What up, y'all? This your boy Ace here.
>> And welcome
>> to So Cabs Y'all. Welcome back on into
the channel, everybody. Man, I hope you
had a wonderful day.
And let's get to this, man. So, we were
just talking about Michael and Willow's
uh conversation and how Michael had to
kind of remind Willow
like, look, um
you're you're trying to get full custody
of the kids and you're trying to get
them away from me completely, but you
got to remember how your kids are going
to be affected by this. You know what I
mean? So, you know, Michael was letting
her know and I think he got through to
her because in this conversation with
Nina,
it does seem like he got through to her.
But before we continue, man, uh if y'all
want to see the full scenes today of
that conversation with Willow and
Michael, I'm going to have that on a
Patreon later.
Um also uh this conversation with her
and Nina as well.
And everything connected with the
storyline, we will have it up on the
channel for you guys, man. But uh
that will be on the Patreon. Thank you
to the new sign-ups that have signed up
as well. Link to the Patreons in the
description box underneath the video,
guys. You can click that link.
So, Willow returned home after visiting
Michael at the Quartermaines uh to talk
to Nina about everything that you
remember, you know, you remember how the
conversation went yesterday with Nina.
Nina was, you know, actually the voice
of reason in that conversation with her
daughter, you know, she was letting her
know that like Michael was really taking
care of her, you know, made sure she got
the bid and all that stuff. But she was
still heated because she thought Michael
was the one that set up, you know, her
being drugged. She still doesn't know
for sure who did it yet, but she
suspects that it was Michael even though
Michael told her you know it wasn't. So,
um
So,
Willow was basically just telling Nina,
you know, Michael has nothing left and
the kids are going to move back
with her full-time, right? And but she
said that she won't cut Michael out of
her out of their lives completely. This
is how I know that Michael
uh
did get the Willow because she did say
that she won't cut Michael out of their
lives completely.
But uh he will only see them on her
terms, which means they're still going
to be in a fight with this situation,
man. So,
but it does mean that Willow's not, you
know, trying to, you know, completely
cut Michael out of their lives like she
was trying to do when she first came
over to the quarter mains.
But she also said she's going to make
the decisions from now on, which means
Michael truly is the one that has to
fight for her children. But there's a
twist to this. And we're going to get to
this in the next video.
Yeah, we got to talk about this with
y'all. So,
Trina and Kai stepped up to the plate.
Trina and Kai stepped up to the plate
and finally told Michael
what they know.
Finally, I mean this is what When did
they find out back in January, bro? It's
August now, almost the goddamn fall, and
they're just telling him.
Uh this is crazy. Let's go over in that
video next, man. Go on ahead and give me
your thoughts here. Short video here.
Give this video a like, share,
subscribe, you guys. Thank you guys for
watching this one. So catch y'all.